[{
    "isShow":true,
    "deviceid":"450500392",
    "userid":"李雷",
    "problem":"蓝牙锁问题",
    "position":"武汉理工大学",
    "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
    "reportstate":"已受理",
    "singletime":"2018-09-19",
    "handler":"李寒",
    "handlerphone":"14083858292",
    "reportfeedback":"完成"

  },{
      "isShow":true,
      "deviceid":"39581083021",
      "userid":"张城",
      "problem":"蓝牙问题",
      "position":"南湖校区",
      "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
      "reportstate":"未受理",
      "singletime":"2018-08-10",
      "handler":"张龙",
      "handlerphone":"49284928381",
      "reportfeedback":"未完成"

  },{
    "isShow":true,
    "deviceid":"450500392",
    "userid":"李雷",
    "problem":"蓝牙锁问题",
    "position":"武汉理工大学",
    "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
    "reportstate":"已受理",
    "singletime":"2018-09-19",
    "handler":"李寒",
    "handlerphone":"14083858292",
    "reportfeedback":"完成"

  },{
      "isShow":true,
      "deviceid":"39581083021",
      "userid":"张城",
      "problem":"蓝牙问题",
      "position":"南湖校区",
      "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
      "reportstate":"未受理",
      "singletime":"2018-08-10",
      "handler":"张龙",
      "handlerphone":"49284928381",
      "reportfeedback":"未完成"

  },{
    "isShow":true,
    "deviceid":"450500392",
    "userid":"李雷",
    "problem":"蓝牙锁问题",
    "position":"武汉理工大学",
    "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
    "reportstate":"已受理",
    "singletime":"2018-09-19",
    "handler":"李寒",
    "handlerphone":"14083858292",
    "reportfeedback":"完成"

  },{
      "isShow":true,
      "deviceid":"39581083021",
      "userid":"张城",
      "problem":"蓝牙问题",
      "position":"南湖校区",
      "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
      "reportstate":"未受理",
      "singletime":"2018-08-10",
      "handler":"张龙",
      "handlerphone":"49284928381",
      "reportfeedback":"未完成"

  },{
    "isShow":true,
    "deviceid":"450500392",
    "userid":"李雷",
    "problem":"蓝牙锁问题",
    "position":"武汉理工大学",
    "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
    "reportstate":"已受理",
    "singletime":"2018-09-19",
    "handler":"李寒",
    "handlerphone":"14083858292",
    "reportfeedback":"完成"

  },{
      "isShow":true,
      "deviceid":"39581083021",
      "userid":"张城",
      "problem":"蓝牙问题",
      "position":"南湖校区",
      "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
      "reportstate":"未受理",
      "singletime":"2018-08-10",
      "handler":"张龙",
      "handlerphone":"49284928381",
      "reportfeedback":"未完成"

  },{
    "isShow":true,
    "deviceid":"450500392",
    "userid":"李雷",
    "problem":"蓝牙锁问题",
    "position":"武汉理工大学",
    "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
    "reportstate":"已受理",
    "singletime":"2018-09-19",
    "handler":"李寒",
    "handlerphone":"14083858292",
    "reportfeedback":"完成"

  },{
      "isShow":true,
      "deviceid":"39581083021",
      "userid":"张城",
      "problem":"蓝牙问题",
      "position":"南湖校区",
      "reporttime":"2018-09-11",
      "reportstate":"未受理",
      "singletime":"2018-08-10",
      "handler":"张龙",
      "handlerphone":"49284928381",
      "reportfeedback":"未完成"

  }]